Guide to the Duke University Press Records, 1812-2019 UA.07.08.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Marketing Files, 1994-2015; 10
  - General Marketing Files, 11.1
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Wallach, Jeremy, ed. Metal Rules the Globe: Heavy Metal, 2008-2012 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Wallach Orig. Review Slip (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: WALLACH Ads (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Wallach Publicity, 2011-2013 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Wallach Reviews, 2012-2014 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Wallach postcard, 2011 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Taylor, Timothy; Music, Sound, and Technology, 2006-2012 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Taylor Orig. Review Slip (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Taylor Publicity, 2011-2013 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Taylor Reviews, 2012-2014 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Taylor Ads (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Sunder Rajan; Biocapital: c, 2004-2008 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Sunder Publicity, 2004-2015 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Sunder Original Review Slip, 2006 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Sunder Reviews, 2006-2008 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Sunder Ads, 2005-2006 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Sunder Copy and Blurbs, 2005-2006 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Starn, Orin; The Passion of Tiger Woods, 2011-2012 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Starn Orig. Review Slip (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Starn Publicity, 2011-2012 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Starn Reviews, 2012-2014 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Starn Ads (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Slobodian, Quinn; Foreign Front, 2010-2011 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Slobodian Orig. Review Slip (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Slobodian Publicity, 2011-2012 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Slobodian Reviews, 2012-2014 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Slobodian Ads (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Ramirez, Sergio; Adios Muchachos, 2009-2012 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Ramirez Publicity, 2011 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Ramirez Reviews, 2012-2014 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Ramirez Ads (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Sigal, Pete; The Flower and the Scorpion: c, 2005-2011 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Sigal Publicity, 2011-2012 (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Sigal Orig. Review Slips (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Sigal Ads (Box 49)
    - Spring 2012 Marketing Files: Sigal Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 49)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fallaw, Ben; Between Salvation and Revolution, 2008-2012 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fallaw / Original Review Slip, 2013 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fallaw / Copy and Blurbs (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fallaw / Ads (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fallaw / Reviews, 2013-2015 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fallaw \ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Dumit; Drugs for Life, 2005-2012 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Dumit \ Publicity, 2012-2015 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Dumit \ Reviews, 2012-2015 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Dumit \ Ads (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Dumit / Copy and Blurbs, 2004-2012 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Dumit \ Original Review Slip (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Dinshaw, Carolyn; Time After Time: Temporal Experience, 2009-2012 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Dinshaw \ Publicity, 2012-2015 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Dinshaw / Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Dinshal \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Dinshaw / Original Review Slip (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Dave, Naisargi; Queer Activism in India, 2010-2011 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Dave \ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Dave / Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Dave/ Original Review Slip (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Dave/ Copy and Blurbs (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Cruz, Denise: Transpacific Femininities, 2010-2012 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Cruz / Publicity, 2012-2014 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Cruz / Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Cruz / Copy and Blurbs (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Cruz / Original Review Slip (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Chong, Doryun; MoMA Book, 2011-2012 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Chong \ Blurbs and Reviews, 2012-2014 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Chong \ Original Review Slip, 2013 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Chong \ Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Chong \ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Chong \ Ads (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Chen, Mel; Animacies, 2011-2012 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Chen\ Copy and Blurbs, 2011-2012 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Chen / Original Review Slip (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Chen / Ads (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Chen \ Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Chen\ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Carter, Miguel; Challenging Social Inequality, 2006-2015 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Carter / Original Review Slip, 2015 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Carter\ Copy and Blurbs, 2012-2015 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Carter / Ads, 2014 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Carter \ Publicity, 2012-2014 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Canessa, Andrew; Intimate Indigeneities, 2010-2012 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Canessa \ Publicity, 2012-2014 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Canessa \ Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Canessa \ Original Review Slip (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Canessa \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Canessa \ Ads (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Akcan, Esra; Architecture in Translation, 2010-2012 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Akcan Publicity, 2012-2014 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Akcan Cover Copy (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Akcan Orig Review Slips (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Akcan Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Abdur-Rahman, Aliyyah; The Erotics of Race, 2010-2012 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Abdur-Rahman / Original Review Slip (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Abdur-Rahman \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Abdur-Rahman \ Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Abdur-Rahman / Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 50)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Imada, Adria L.; Aloha America, 2006-2012 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Imada Reviews, 2012-2014 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Imada Publicity, 2012-2014 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Imada \ Ads (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Imada \ Original Review Slip (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Imada \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Hopkinson, Natalie; Go-Go in the Chocolate City, 2009-2012 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Hopkinson Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Hopkinson Cover Copy (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Hopkinson Reviews, 2012-2015 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Hopkinson Orig. Review Slip (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Hopkinson Postcard, 2011-2012 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Hopkinson Ads (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Heller: Post-Indusrial Peasants, 2010-2013 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Heller \ Publicity, 2012-2014 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Heller \ Reviews, 2013-2015 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Heller / Copy and Blurbs (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Heller / Original Review Slip, 2013 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Gupta, Akhil; Red Tape, 2006-2012 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Gupta: Publicity, 2012-2014 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: ADS: Gupta (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Gupta: Cover Copy (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Gupta: Original Review Slip, 2012-2015 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Gupta Reviews, 2012-2015 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Gorski, Philip; Bordieusian Theory, 2009-2012 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Gorski \ Original Review Slips, 2013 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Gorski \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Gorski / Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Gorski \ Publicity, 2012-2014 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Goldstein, David; Outlawed, 2011-2012 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Goldstein \ Publicity, 2012-2014 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Goldstein \ Reviews, 2012-2015 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Goldstein \ Ads (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Goldstein \ Original Review Slip (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Goldstein \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fuqua, Joy V.; Ill Effects, 2011 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fuqua Cover Copy (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fuqua Publicity, 2012-2014 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fuqua Orig. Review Slip (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fuqua Reviews, 2013 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Frederik, Laurie; Trumpets in the Mountains, 2010-2012 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Frederik \ Publicity, 2012-2014 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Frederik \ Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Frederik / Ads (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Frederik \ Original Review Slip (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Frederik \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Forman, Murray; One Night on TV, 2011-2012 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Forman \ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Forman \ Reviews, 2012-2013 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Forman \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Forman \ Original Review Slip (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fisher, Melissa; Wall Street Women, 2010-2012 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fisher / Copy and Blurbs (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fisher / Ads (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fisher / Reviews, 2012-2014 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fisher \ Publicity, 2012-2015 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fisher \ Original Review Slip (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fisher-e F12, 2012-2014 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fischer, Frank, ed.; The Argumentative Turn Revisited, 2008-2011 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fischer \ Publicity, 2012-2016 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fischer \ Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fischer \ Ads (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fischer \ Original Review Slip (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Fischer \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Feld, Steven; Sound and Sentiment, 2011-2012 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Feld / Original Review Slips (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Feld \ Ads, 1985-2012 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Feld \ Ads (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Feld \ Reviews, 2012-2014 (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Feld \ Publicity (Box 51)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mumford, Jeremy; Vertical Empire: Urbanism, Ethnography and the "General Resettlement of the Indians", 2011 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mumford \ Ads (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mumford \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mumford \ Original Review Slip (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mumford / Publicity, 2011-2015 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mumford \ Reviews, 2013-2015 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mumford, Jeremy; Vertical Empire: Colonial Andes, 2009 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mckiernan-Gonzalez, John; Fevered Measures: Connecting Public Health and Race, 2008-2013 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mckiernan-Gonzalez \ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mckiernan-Gonzalez / Reviews, 2012-2014 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mckiernan-Gonzalez / Ads (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mckiernan-Gonzalez \ Copy and Blurbs, 2008-2012 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mckiernan-Gonzalez \ Original Review Slip (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mavor, Carol; Black and Blue, 2010-2011 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mavor \ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mavor \ Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mavor \ Copy and Blurbs, 2011-2012 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mavor \ Original Review Slip (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mankeekar, Purnima and Schein, Laisa; Media, Erotics, and Transnational Asia, 2006-2012 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mankeekar and Shein \ Publicity, 2013 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mankeekar and Shein \ Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mankekar and Schein \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mankekear \ Original Review Slip, 2013 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mahoney, Michael: The Other Zulus, 2005-2011 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mahoney / Reviews, 2013-2015 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mahoney / Ads (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mahoney / Original Review Slip (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mahoney / Copy and Blurbs (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Mahoney / Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Lefebvre, Alexandre; Bergson, Politics, and Religion, 2009-2011 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Lefebvre \ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Lefebvre \ Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Lefebvre / Ads (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Lefebvre / Copy and Blurbs (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Lefebvre \ Original Review Slip (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Lee, Esther; Seven Contemporary Plays, 2010-2012 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Lee \ Original Review Slip (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Lee \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Lee \ Reviews, 2012-2013 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Lee \ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Kun, Josh; Re-Assembling Tijuana, 2009-2011 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Kun \ Original Review Slip (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Kun / Copy and Blurbs (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Kun \ Reviews, 2012-2014 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Kun \ Ads (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Kun, Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Kommers, Donald P.; The Constitutional Jurisprudence of the Federal Republic of Germany, 2011-2012 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Kommers / Original Review Slip (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Kommers / Copy and Blurbs (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Kommers / Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Knaus, John Kenneth; The Hardy Himalayan Orphan, 2010-2014 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Knaus Reviews, 2012-2013 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Knaus Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Knaus Cover Copy (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Keaton, Tricia; Black France: France Noire, 2009-2012 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Keaton \ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Keaton \ Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Keaton \ Ads (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Keaton \ Original Review Slip (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Keaton \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Joseph, Ralina; Transcending Blackness, 2010-2012 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Joseph \ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Joseph \ Reviews, 2013-2015 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Joseph \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Joseph \ Original Review Slip (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Inhorn, M & E. Wentzell; Medical Anthro @ Inter., 2010-2012 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Inhorn \ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Inhorn / Reviews, 2013 (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Inhorn / Ads (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Inhorn / Copy and Blurbs (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Inhorn / Original Review Slip (Box 52)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Stahl, Matt; Unfree Masters, 2011-2012 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Stahl \ Reviews, 2012-2013 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Stahl \ Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Stahl \ Original Review Slip (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Stahl \ Copy and Blurbs, 2011 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Skotnes, Andor; Social Struggles in Baltimore, 2010-2012 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Skotnes / Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Skotnes / Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Skotnes / Ads (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Skotnes / Copy and Blurbs (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Skotnes / Original Review Slip (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Schulman, Sarah; Salt on Green Almonds: A Personal Journey to Israel/Palestine and the Queer International, 2011-2012 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Schulman \ Publicity, 2012-2014 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Schulman \ Reviews, 2012-2015 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Schulman \ Ads, 2015 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Schulman / Copy and Blurbs (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Scales, Chris; Recording Culture, 2010-2011 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Scales / Blurbs and Copy (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Scales / Original Review Slip, 2013 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Scales / Ads (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Scales \ Publicity, 2012-2015 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Scales \ Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Rosas, Gilbert; Barrio Libre, 2009-2011 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Rosas \ Review, 2013-2015 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Rosas / Copy and Blurbs (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Rosas \ Original Review Slip (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Rosas \ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Robbins, Bruce; Pepetual War: Cosmopolitanism from the Viewpoint of Violence, 2010-2011 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Robbins \ Reviews, 2012-2013 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Robbins / Ads (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Robbins \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Robbins \ Original Review Slip (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Robbins \ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Romney, Joshua; The Hermetic Deleuze, 2009-2011 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Romney \ Reviews, 2013 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Romney \ Ads (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Romney \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Romney \ Original Review Slip (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Romney \ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Rama, Angel; Narrative Transculturation in Latin America, 2005-2012 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Rama \ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Rama \ Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Rama \ Ads (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Rama \ original review slip (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Rama \ Copy and Blurbs, 2011 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Prentice, Rachel; Bodies in Formation, 2009-2012 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Prentice \ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Prentice \ Reviews, 2013-2015 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Prentice \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Prentice \ Original Review Slip, 2013 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Polloch, Anne; Medicating Race, 2010-2011 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Pollock \ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Pollock \ Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Pollock \ Ads (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Pollock \ Original Review Slip (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Pollock \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Palumbo-Liu, David; The Deliverance of Others, 2010-2012 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Palumbo-Liu \ Publicity, 2011-2013 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Palumbo-Liu \ Copy and Blurbs, 2011-2012 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Palumbo-Liu \ Reviews, 2012-2014 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Palumbo-Liu \ Original Review Slip (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Nguyen; Representing Refugees, 2004-2012 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Nguyen / Publicity, 2012-2014 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Nguyen / Reviews, 2012-2014 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Nguyen / Original Review Slip (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Nguyen / Copy and Blurbs (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Naficy, Hamid; Cinema and Nat'l Identity Vol 3-4, 2011 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Naficy \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Naficy / Publicity, 2012-2015 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Naficy \ Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Naficy \ Ads (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Naficy \ Original Review Slip (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Murphy, Michelle; Seizing the Means of Reproduction, 2009-2012 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Murphy \ Reviews, 2013-2015 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Murphy \ Ads (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Murphy \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Murphy \ Original Review Slips (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Murphy \ Publicity, 2012-2013 (Box 53)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: White, Michelle; Buy it Now, 2009-2011 (Box 54)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: White \ Publicity (Box 54)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: White \ Reviews, 2012-2014 (Box 54)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: White \ Original Review Sheet (Box 54)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: White \ Copy and Blurbs (Box 54)
    - Fall 2012 Marketing Files: Wallace, Maurice O.; Pictures and Progress, 2009-2012 (Box 54)